orduh.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy | OrDuH

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

You might also want to check out our [Terms of Service](https://www.orduh.com/privacy/terms-of-service/) and [Extended Cookies Policy](https://www.orduh.com/privacy/extended-cookies-policy/) pages as well.

 **What information do we collect?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your Name, Email address, Mailing address, Phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

 **When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or enter information on our site.

 **How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize user’s experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to better serve you.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

 **How do we protect visitor information?**

We use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.

We do not use an SSL certificate

  * We only provide articles and information, and we never ask for personal or private information

 **Do we use ‘cookies’?**  
**We use cookies to:**

  * Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits,
  * Keep track of advertisements,

It won’t affect the users experience

 **Third Party Disclosure**

We may transfer your non-identifiable information to third parties. We may also transfer your identifiable information, but only to trusted third parties

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Google**

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **We have implemented the following:**

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * DoubleClick Platform Integration

 **We and third party vendors such as Google use:**

To compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.  
Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act**

 **According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:**

Users can visit our site anonymously

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above.  
Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:

  * On our Privacy Policy Page

Users are able to change their personal information:

  * By emailing us

 **How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor them and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.  
**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

We allow

 **COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

We do not specifically market to children under 13

 **Fair Information Practices**

 **In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via email

  * Within 7 business days

We will notify the users via in site notification

  * Within 1 business day

We agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors

 **CAN SPAM Act**

 **We collect your email address:**

To send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

To market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to your clients after the original transaction has occured  
**To be accordance with CANSPAM we agree to the following:**

We will NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses

We will identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way

We will include the physical address of our business or site headquarters

We will monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

We will honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly

We will give an ‘opt-out’ or ‘unsubscribe’ option

 **  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can**

  * Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **Contact Information**

Jesse Hackshaw

22 Lodge Village

Kingstown

St. Vincent

VC0100

info@orduh.com

TL:DR

Affiliate Disclaimer

Some of the products mentioned on this site may include an affiliate link and provide Orduh and its owner(s) and contributes with of monetary earnings.

Privacy Policy

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [ **here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site.

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by emailing us at info |-at-| orduh.com

With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, Google, VibrantMedia, and other third-party ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to users based on their visit to this site and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ **Google ad and content network privacy policy**](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).
  * Users may opt out of other cookies by clicking [ **here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the above address.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to all information [including proprietary information] that we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries).

Consumers can access or correct this information by e-mail us at the above address.

With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses.
